Guide to the Three Arrows Cooperative Society, Inc. Records TAM.250
Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives
- Series III: Unprocessed Materials, 1930's-2000's; 299723
  - News Flyers and Journals, 2000's; 299790 (Box 10)
  - Ledgers, 1950's-1980's; 299791 (Box 11)
- Series IV: 2011 Addendum, undated; 438708
  - Account Book ("Three Arrows Costs") of William Vladeck, son of Baruch Charney Vladek, 1941-1945; 438790 (Box 12, Folder 1)
  - Board Meetings, 2009-2011; 438791 (Box 12, Folder 2)
  - By-Laws and Proprietary Release, 1979; 438792 (Box 12, Folder 3)
  - Dock, 2005, 2009; 438793 (Box 12, Folder 4)
  - External Publications, 2008-2011; 438794 (Box 12, Folder 5)
  - Financial Audit, 1979; 438795 (Box 12, Folder 6)
  - Internal Publications, 1986-2011; 438796 (Box 12, Folder 7)
  - Labor Day Shows, 2008-2011; 438797 (Box 12, Folder 8)
  - Long Range Planning, 2010; 438798 (Box 12, Folder 9)
  - Membership Meetings, 1986-2011; 438799 (Box 12, Folder 10)
  - Treasurer's Reports, 2008-2010; 438800 (Box 12, Folder 11)
  - Voice of the Hill, 2008; 438801 (Box 12, Folder 12)
  - Voice of the Hill, 2009; 438802 (Box 12, Folder 12)
  - Voice of the Hill, 2010; 438803 (Box 12, Folder 12)
  - Voice of the Hill, 2011; 438804 (Box 12, Folder 12)
- Series V: Photographs, 1940s-2006; 496893
  - Anniversary, 70th: Exhibition I, [2006]; 496894 (Box 12, Folder 16)
  - Anniversary, 70th: Exhibition II, [2006]; 496895 (Box 12, Folder 17)
  - Anniversary, 70th: Exhibition (Captions), [2006]; 496896 (Box 12, Folder 18)
  - Anniversary, 70th: Exhibition (Oversize), [2006]; 496915 (Flat-file 1, Drawer 2)
  - Anniversary, 70th: Exhibition (Photographs), [2006]; 496897 (Box 12, Folder 19)
  - Anniversary, 70th: Exhibition (Print and Graphic Materials), [2006]; 496898 (Box 12, Folder 20)
  - General Photographs, 1940s-1950s; 496899 (Box 12, Folder 21)
  - General Photographs, circa 1960s; 496900 (Box 12, Folder 22)
  - General Photographs, 1964-1967; 496901 (Box 12, Folder 23)
  - General Photographs, 1968; 496902 (Box 12, Folder 24)
  - General Photographs, 1970s; 496903 (Box 12, Folder 25)
  - General Photographs, 1990s; 496904 (Box 12, Folder 26)
  - General Photographs, 2000s; 496916 (Box 12, Folder 27)
  - General Photographs I, undated; 496905 (Box 12, Folder 28)
  - General Photographs II, undated; 496906 (Box 12, Folder 29)
  - General Photographs (Oversize), 1998, undated; 496917 (Flat-file 1, Drawer 2)
  - Landscape Photographs, undated; 496907 (Box 12, Folder 30)
  - Watercolors, 1999; 496908 (Box 12, Folder 31, Box 15)
  - Justus and Jenny Ebert, 1889-1945 (Box 12, Folder 32)
- Series VI: Maps and Plans, 1937-1981; 478926
  - New Community Bulding Plan, 1952; 478933 (Flat-file 7, Drawer 12)
  - Norman Thomas Hall Plan, 1952; 478937 (Flat-file 7, Drawer 12)
  - Property Layout and Names, 1939-1940; 478928 (Flat-file 7, Drawer 12)
  - Putnam Valley Plan, Rochdale Road, 1948; 478927 (Flat-file 7, Drawer 12)
  - Social Hall Plan, 1952; 478938 (Flat-file 7, Drawer 12)
  - Three Arrows and Vicinity, 1968; 478932 (Flat-file 7, Drawer 12)
  - Three Arrows Property Map [Original and 2 copies], 1963; 478939 (Flat-file 7, Drawer 12)
  - Three Arrows Sites and Names, 1966; 478930 (Flat-file 7, Drawer 12)
  - Three Arrows Structures and Site Locations, undated; 478935 (Flat-file 7, Drawer 12)
  - Three Arrows Survey and Plan [2 sheets], 1937; 478934 (Flat-file 7, Drawer 12)
  - United States Department of the Interior Geological Survey: Mohegan Lake Quadrangle, 1981; 478929 (Flat-file 7, Drawer 12)
- Series VII: 2014 Addendum, 1941-2014; 586702
  Scope and Content Note
  This series contains materials that was donated to the library in 2014, with materials dating from the early 1940s up until 2014. The materials include budget documentation; board of directors and membership meeting minutes reporting on Three Arrows committees; by-laws; plays, songs, and poetry possibly performed at the cooperative; programs of performances; correspondence between members regarding the governance of Three Arrows; and their newsletter, The Voice of the Hill.
  - Flash drive, 2010-2014; 586703 (Box 13, Folder 1)
  - Budget Information, 2011-2014; 586704 (Box 13, Folder 2)
  - Meeting minutes, 2012-2013; 586705 (Box 13, Folder 3)
  - Plays, Poems, and other Writings related to Three Arrows, 1960s; 586706 (Box 13, Folder 4)
  - Correspondence related to Governance of Three Arrows, 2012-2013; 586707 (Box 13, Folder 5)
  - Labor Day Shows, 1941-2013; 586708 (Box 13, Folder 6)
  - Camp Play Photograph with Bobb Vladeck and Betsy Bosworth, circa 1953-1954; 586709 (Box 13, Folder 7)
  - Songs, 1940s-1960s; 586710 (Box 13, Folder 8)
  - The Voice of the Hill, 2011; 586711 (Box 13, Folder 9)
  - The Voice of the Hill, 2012; 586712 (Box 13, Folder 10)
  - The Voice of the Hill, 2013; 586713 (Box 13, Folder 11)
  - The Voice of the Hill, 1956-1993; 586714 (Box 13, Folder 12)
- Series VIII: Archived Website, Mar 1, 2015-ongoing; 586716
  The Three Arrows Cooperative Society, Inc. is the successor organization to the Barger Street Cooperative Society, chartered in 1937. Early members purchased 125 acres of farmland in Putnam Valley, NY and formed a cooperative summer colony which eventually grew to include 75 individual units. The colony, sometimes known as Camp Three Arrows, is modeled on socialist and communitarian values and offers residents a wide range of cultural, educational and leisure activities. The website contains information on property listings, news articles about the the co-op, planning meeting listings, and other information.
- Series IX: 2015 Addendum, 1997-2015; 591809
  Arrangement
  This collection has not been arranged by an archivist. The materials are arranged in the order in which they were received from the donor.
  The accretion includes meeting notes, correspondence, brochures, financial records, board membership lists, property leases, and administrative documents produced by the Three Arrows Cooperative Society during the period of 1997-2015.
  - The Voice of the Hill, 2014; 592796 (Box 14, Folder 1)
  - Membership Lists, circa 2014-2015; 592797 (Box 14, Folder 2)
  - Administrative Records, 2014-2015; 592798 (Box 14, Folder 3)
  - Meetings, 2014-2015; 592799 (Box 14, Folder 4-5)
  - The Voice of the Hill, 2015; 592800 (Box 14, Folder 6)
  - Board of Directors, 1997-1998; 592801 (Box 14, Folder 7)
- Series X. 2017 Addendum
  - Labor Day Show, 2005-2015 (Box 16, Folder 1-11)
  - Labor Day Show (Henry Marguiles), circa 1960s-1970s (Box 16, Folder 12)
  - Board Meetings, 2016 (Box 16, Folder 13)
  - Committee Reports, 2016 (Box 16, Folder 14)
  - Internal Publications, 2016 (Box 16, Folder 15)
  - Membership Meetings, 2016 (Box 16, Folder 16)
  - The Voice of the Hill, 2016 (Box 16, Folder 17)
  - 80th Anniversary Party, 2016 (Box OS009, Folder 1)
  - Panorama of Tenth Anniversary of the Barger Co-Operative Society, Henry Hudson Hotel, 1947 (Box XOS003)